A Guide to the Across the Way Productions, Inc., 2002-2016
Radford University, University Archives, McConnell Library
University Archives, McConnell Library, Radford University
Across the Way Productions, Inc., 2002-2016
University Archives, McConnell Library, Radford University
AC 035
9.5 Linear feet, 1,090 photographs, 3 mini discs, 6 videotapes, 5 linear feet of C.D's.
Across the Way Productions Inc. was founded in 2002 by Kris Hodges and Erika Johnson. The two wished to create a world music festival in Floyd, Virginia and thus Floyd Fest began in September of 2002. This collection features materials from the events Floyd Fest, Floyd Fandango, Vintage Virginia Wine and Food Festival, Virginia Wine Festival, Capital City Carnival and Microbrew Fest, Totally Rad Roanoke Star City Concert Series and The Phoenix all created by Across the Way Productions, Inc. Materials include advertising/promotional items, graphic design elements, the organization and logistics of the events, newspaper clippings, photographs, videos, live discs and mini discs of the events.
Across the Way Productions, Inc.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Across the Way Productions, Inc.
Accruals
Further additions to the collection are expected.
Biographical/Historical Information
Across the Way Productions, Inc. was founded in June 2000 by Kris Hodges in the town of Floyd, Virginia. His wife, Erika Johnson, was also opening her business, Oddfella's Cantina, simultaneously. The company was founded on the premise of bringing a world music festival to the town of Floyd, Virginia. The company sponsors events such as Floyd Fandango, Capital City Carnival and Microbrew Fest, Vintage Virginia Wine and Food Festival and much more. The company's most famous event is Floyd Fest, a music festival featuring artists from all over the globe, which takes place for 5 days each July. Oddfella's was sold in 2002 for funds to start Floyd Fest. Floyd Fandango is hosted near the fourth of July. Begun in 2009, it did not take place during the years 2012-2015, as the company needed time to make the festival more profitable. Floyd Fandango now draws crowds to the reimagined fest, which now includes outdoor sports and a farm to table dinner in addition to the staples of the festival- beer, cider, and wine tastings, workshops and performances by bands that also frequent Floyd Fest. The company expanded into Northern Virginia with its Capital Carnival and Microbrew Fest, the Vintage Virginia Wine and Food Festival and the Virginia Wine Festival in 2007. Since the Vintage Virginia Wine and Food Festival had operated close to 3 decades, partnering with the event helped the company gain notoriety and establish themselves. In 2016, Across the Way Productions Inc. launched the Totally Rad Roanoke Star City Concert Series, which featured Huey Lewis and The News, Blondie, and Brian Wilson of the Beach Boys' 50th Anniversary of the album "Pet Sounds," that took place at Roanoke's Elmwood Park Amphitheater. Also in 2016, The Phoenix was started as a venue in Roanoke, Virginia. A nod to the battle of the bands format of the 80's and 90's, visitors to the Phoenix receive a token and votes for their favorite band at the end of the night. The winners of the battles go on to compete in Floyd Fests Annual On-The-Rise Artist Competition. The Phoenix battle of the bands competition was renewed for a second year and took place in 2017.
Scope and Content
This collection features materials from Across the Way, Inc. located in Floyd, Virginia. It includes 5 linear inches of advertising material such as flyers, post cards, coasters and stickers for the events of Floyd Fest, Floyd Fandango, Vintage Virginia Wine and Food Festival, Virginia Wine Festival, Capital City Carnival and Microbrew Fest, Totally Rad Roanoke Star City Concert Series and The Phoenix, which were all created by the company 1.5 linear feet of oversize advertising materials are present in this collection. 5 linear inches of graphic designs for the events are included encompassing access, parking and camping passes and bracelets, tickets and schedule of events pamphlets. Also included with graphic materials are accomplishments and accolades of the company and its events such as a proclamation from the city of Roanoke. 3 linear inches of organization of the events created by the company are present in this collection and include job descriptions of staff, logistical details, business plans and other reports of that nature, catering plans, maps of the festivals grounds, performer travel and performance organization and FAQ information. 1,090 pictures show mainly daily happenings at various Floyd Fests, but also showcase Capital City Carnival and Microbrew Fest, Vintage Virginia Wine and Food Festival and the Wine Down the Music Trail Festival and a trip to Ghana to search out talent for Floyd Fest. 1.5 linear feet of oversize photographs are also included in this collection. 2 linear inches of newspaper articles and clippings are also available in this collection and deal exclusively with Floyd Fest. These newspaper articles and clippings document the years of 2002-2015. There is approximately 1 linear foot of multimedia items in this collection that comprise of videos, mini discs and C.D.'s. Videotapes record live shows and show an interview with Kris Hodges on Virginia Tonight. Mini discs hold recordings of live performances as well. The C.D's account for 5 linear feet of the multimedia series and are of live performances done during various Floyd Fests and feature bands such as Donna the Buffalo, Trampling Turtles and African Showboys. As well as commercial C.D's produced from various Floyd Fests and other miscellaneous C.D's originally intended for private use.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in chronological order with the exception of the live discs, which are arranged alphabetically in their respective binders in six series, all of which have been further organized into subseries. The series and subseries arrangement is as follows:
Series 1: Advertising/Promotional Material
1.1 Floyd Fest, 2002-2016
1.2 Floyd Fandango, 2007-2016
1.3 Vintage Virginia Food and Wine Festival, 2007-2015
1.4 Virginia Wine Festival, 2009-2015
1.5 Totally Rad Roanoke Star City Concert Series, 2016
1.6 Capital City Carnival and Microbrew Fest, 2007
1.7 The Phoenix, 2006
Series 2: Graphic Design for Festivals
2.1 Floyd Fest, 2002-2016
2.2 Floyd Fandango, 2010-2016
2.3 Vintage Virginia Food and Wine Festival, 2006-2015
2.4 Virginia Wine Festival, 2009-2015
2.5 Totally Rad Roanoke Star City Concert Series, Undated
2.6 Capital City Carnival and Microbrew Fest, 2007
2.7 Accomplishments and Accolades, 2005-2011
Series 3: Organization of the Festival
3.1 Floyd Fest, 2002-2015
3.2 Floyd Fest Performers, 2004-2006
3.3 Floyd Fandango, Undated
3.4 Capital City Carnival and Microbrew Fest, 2007
3.5 Sponsorship Information, 2002-2004
Series 4: Newspaper Articles
4.1 Floyd Fest, 2002-2015
Series 5: Photographs and Multimedia
5.1 Assorted Photographs of Across the Way Productions Events, 2002-2014
5.2 Video Tapes, 2002-2003
5.3 Mini Discs, 2002
Series 6: Live Discs
6.1 Commercial Collectors C.D's, 2002-2012
6.2 Miscellaneous C.D's, 2001-2012
6.3 Floyd Fest- July 26-29, 2007
6.4 Vintage Virginia, 2010
6.5 Fandango, 2010
6.6 Floyd Fest 8- July 23-26, 2009
6.7 Floyd Fest 7- July 24-27, 2008
6.8 Floyd Fest 9- July 22-25, 2010
6.9 Floyd Fest X- July 28- 31, 2011
6.10 Floyd Fest 11- July 26-29, 2012
Subject Terms
Johnson, Erika
Hodges,Kris
Across the Way Productions, Inc.
Floyd Fest
Capital City Carnival and Microbew Fest
Floyd Fandango
Oddfella's Cantina
The Phoenix--Across the Way Productions, Inc.
Totally Rad Roanoke Star City Concert Series
Vintage Virginia Food and Wine Festival
Virginia Wine Festival
Virginia, Floyd
Virginia, Roanoke
Virginia, Southwest-- Music Festival
Contents List
- 1.Advertising/Promotional Material, 2002-2016
  - 1.1 Floyd Fest, 2002-2016
    - Floyd Fest 1 Posters September 27-29, 2002 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 1)
    - Floyd Fest 2 Posters, August 15-17, 2003 (Box Ovesize 1, Folder 2)
    - Floyd Fest 2 Promotional Campaign, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Floyd Fest 3 Posters, August 13-15, 2004 (Box Oversize, Folder 3)
    - Floyd Fest Flyers, Cards and Postcards (1 of 2), 2005-2013 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Floyd Fest Flyers, Cards and Postcards (2 of 2), 2005-2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Floyd Fest 4 Posters, July 29-31, 2005 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - Floyd Fest 6 Posters, July 26-29, 2007 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    - Floyd Fest 7 Posters, July 24-27, 2008 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - 2010 Promotional Material (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Floyd Fest 9 Posters, Jul 22-25, 2010 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - Floyd Fest 10 Posters, July 28-31, 2011 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 8)
    - Floyd Fest 11 Posters, July 26-29, 2012 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 9)
    - 2013 AtWP Ads ( 1of 2), 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 2013 AtWP Ads (2 of 2), 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - General Floyd Fest Promotional Campaign, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Floyd Fest 12 Promotional Campaign, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Floyd Fest 12 Posters, July 25-28, 2013 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 10)
    - Floyd Fest Stickers, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Showdown Throwdown Posters, June 20, 2015 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 11)
    - Floyd Fest 14 Posters, July 22-26, 2015 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 12)
    - Floyd Fest 16 Posters, July 27-31, 2016 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 13)
  - 1.2 Floyd Fandango
    - Floyd Fandango Flyers, 2009-2016 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Floyd Fandango Posters, 2009-2016 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 14)
  - 1.3 Vintage Virginia Wine and Food Festival, 2007-2015
    - Vintage Virginia Flyers, 2007-2015 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1.4 Virginia Wine Festival, 2009-2015 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Wine Festival Flyers, 2009-2015 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1.5 Totally Rad Roanoke Star City Concert Series, 2016
    - Star City Concert Series Flyers and Stickers, April 20-August 20, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1.6 Capital City Carnival and Microbrew Fest, 2007
    - Capital City Carnival Flyers, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1.7 The Phoenix, 2016
    - The Phoenix Posters, April - October, 2016 (Box Oversize 1, Folder 15)
- 2. Graphic Designs for Festivals, 2002-2016
  - 2.1 Floyd Fest, 2002-2016
    - Floyd Fest Access, Parking and Camping Passes, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Floyd Fest Tickets & Access Bracelets, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Floyd Fest Schedule of Events Pamphlets (1 of 3), 2002-2011 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Floyd Fest Schedule of Events Pamplets (2 of 3), 2012-2016 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Floyd Fest Schedule of Events Pamphlet (3 of 3), 2015 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 2.2 Floyd Fandango, 2010-2016
    - Floyd Fandango Access Passes, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 2010 Floyd Fandango Tickets (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 2.3 Vintage Virginia Wine and Food Festival, 2006-2015
    - Vintage Virginia Access Passes, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Vintage Virginia Schedule of Events Pamphlet, 2007-2015 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 2.4 Virginia Wine Festival, 2009-2015
    - Virginia Wine Festival Access Passes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Wine Festival Schedule of Events Pamphlet, 2009-2015 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 2.5 Totally Rad Roanoke Star City Concert Series, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Star City Concert Series Access Passes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 2.6 Capital City Carnival and Microbrew Fest, 2007
    - Capital City Carnival Schedule of Events Pamphlet and Access Passes, September, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 2.7 Accomplishments and Accolades, 2005-2011
    - Accomplishments and Accolades - General, 2005-2011 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 3. Organization of the Festival
  - 3.1 Floyd Fest, 2002-2015
    - Floyd Fest Reports, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Floyd Fest 2 Logistical Details, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Floyd Fest Job Descriptions of Staff, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - General Organization Information - Floyd Fest, 2004-2015 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Post Floyd Fest Ideas for Improvement, 2005-2007 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Floyd Fest 5 FAQ, July, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Floyd Fest Catering Plan, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Floyd Fest Maps of Grounds, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 3.2 Floyd Fest Performers, 2004-2006
    - General Performer Information - Floyd Fest, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Performer Travel and Performance Organization, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 3.3 Floyd Fandango, Undated
    - Floyd Fandango FAQ, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 3.4 Capital City Carnival and Microbrew Fest, 2007
    - General Organizational Information - Capital City Carnival, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 3.5 Sponsorship Information, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Sponsorship at Floyd Fest, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 4. Newspaper Articles
  - 4.1 Floyd Fest, 2002-2015
    - Floyd Fest Newspaper Articles, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Floyd Fest Newspaper Articles, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Floyd Fest Newspaper Articles, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Floyd Fest Newspaper Articles, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Floyd Fest Newspaper Articles, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Floyd Fest Newspaper Articles, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Floyd Fest Newspaper Articles, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Floyd Fest Newspaper Articles, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Floyd Fest Newspaper Articles, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- 5. Photographs and Multimedia
  Scope and Content
  Photographs of various activities from Floyd Fest and Capital City Carnival Events are housed in a folder and packed inside the box horizontally. Subjects of these photographs include Floyd Fest Field Day held on 6/22/02, various photographs from Floyd Fests 2002-2014, Capital City Carnival performances, pictures of a trip to Ghana, and photographs of the Wine Down the Music Trail Wine Festival in 2005. Photographs in sleeves are from the 2002 Floyd Fest (photographer Russ Helgren) and the Wine Down the Music Trail Wine Festival held in 2005. Folders denoting an OS mean that folder has been moved to an oversize box.
  - 5.1 Assorted Photographs of Across the Way Productions Inc. Events
    - Miscellaneous Photographs from Floyd Fest and Capital City Carnival Events, 2002-2014 (Box 4)
    - Floyd Fest Photographs, Undated (Box Oversize 1, Folder 16)
  - 5.2 Video Tapes, 2002-2003
    - Floyd Fest B-roll, 2002 (Box 5)
    - Across the Way Floyd WorldFest, 8/23/02 (Box 5)
    - Manipura - Tribal Fusion Bellydance FloydFest, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Floyd Fest 2, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Virginia Tonight Interview with Kris Hodges, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Scofield 1 & 2 GL 1 (#18 & #30) Not Edited, Undated (Box 5)
  - 5.3 Mini Discs, 2002
    - Acoustic Syndicate Floyd Fest Good, 9-29-02 (Box 5)
    - AstroGlides 9/1; Charlie Justin Dich; Bella and Edgerz; Bebop 2nd set 3rd st; Black Twig Pichers; African; J 2 Ponies (Floyd Fest 9-29-02) (Box 5)
    - Blue Tidas 1-6-02, Second Wynde Bums #1, Grisman Flyd 9-29-02 Good, 1/6-9/29/02 (Box 5)
    - Candon, Blank, Undated (Box 5)
- 6. Live Discs and Other C.D's
  This subseries holds C.D's intended for private use that includes live performances and a graphics archive disc, which was created by Radford University Special Collections in April of 2017.
  - 6.1 Commercial Collectors C.D's, 2002-2012
    - 1st Annual Floyd County World Music Festival 2002 Collectors C.D (Box 5)
    - Floyd Fest 5 Roots Alive, July 27-30, 2006 (Box 5)
    - Floyd Fest 7 Family Affair, July 24-27, 2008 (Box 5)
    - Floyd Fest 8 Revival, 2009 (Box 5)
    - Floyd Fest 9 Breaking Ground, 2010 (Box 5)
    - Floyd Fest 9 Breaking Ground, 2010 (Box 5)
    - Floyd Fest 11 Lovers Rock, July 26-29, 2012 (Box 5)
    - Appalachia Music from Home, Undated (Box 5)
  - 6.2 Miscellaneous C.D's, 2001-2012
    - Floyd Fest Graphics Archive 1 & 2 (Bennett), 2001-2005 (Box 5)
    - Floyd Fest Autocad Mapping (Tom Franko), 2012 (Box 5)
    - Floyd Fest Autocad Mapping (Michael Laroche), Undated (Box 5)
  - 6.3 Floyd Fest 6, July 26-29, 2007
    - Barrel House Mamas, 7/26/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Kusun Ensamble, 7/27/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - The Waybacks 1 of 2, 7/27/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - The Waybacks 2 of 2, 7/27/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Carolina Choc. Drops, 7/27-28/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Blue Mule, 7/28/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Donna the Buffalo 1 of 2, 7/28/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Donna the Buffalo 2 of 2, 7/28/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Hackenshaw Boys, 7/28/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Langhorne Slim, 7/28/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - North Mississippi Allstars 1 of 2, 7/28/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - North Mississippi Allstars 2 of 2, 7/28/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - The Waybacks, 7/28/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Scythians, 7/29/07 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Hackenshaw Boys, 7/29/07 (Volume Binder 1)
  - 6.4 Vintage Virginia, 2010
    - Big Sam 1 of 2, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Big Sam 2 of 2, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Big Sam Saturday, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - DJ Williams Saturday, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - KDTU Saturday 1 of 2, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - KDTU 2 of 2, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Jospe Saturday, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - DJ Williams Sunday 1 of 2, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - DJ Williams Sunday 2 of 2, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Jospe Sunday, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
  - 6.5 Fandango, 2010
    - Blue Mule II, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Danger Muffin, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Danger Muffin - Sundae Muffin, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - Disco - My Dear Disco, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
    - BRI - Sun, 2010 (Volume Binder 1)
  - 6.6 Floyd Fest 8, July 23-26, 2009
    - Thursday #1, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Thursday #4, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Friday #1, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Friday #3, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Friday #8, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Saturday #4, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Saturday #5, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Saturday #6, 2009 (Volume Bidner 2)
    - Sunday #1, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Sunday #2, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Sunday #3, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Sunday #4, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Adrienne Young & The Old Faithful, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - American Dumpster, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - American Dumpster, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The Bittersweets 1 of 2, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The Bittersweets 2 of 2, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The Belleville Outfit, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The Belleville Outfit, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The BelleVille Outfit, 7/26/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Blues & Lazers, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Blue Mule, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Blues Traveler, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Blount Harvey, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Crooked Road Presentation (incomplete), 7/26/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - David Shultz & the Skyline, 7/26/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Dryhill Draggers track 1, Jugbusters track 2, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The Duhks, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The Duhks, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Electric Chamelion, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - EOTO 1 of 2, 7/23/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - EOTO 2 of 2, 7/23/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Farrow in the Dark 1 of 2, 7/23/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Farrow in the Dark 2 of 2, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Holy Ghost Tent Revival, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Holy Ghost Tent Revival, 7/26/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Hoorah Cloggers w/ wild turkey, 7/26/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The Horse Flies, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Jesse Chong Band, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Kat Mills #1, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Kat Mills #2, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Kat Mills #3, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Lee Boys late night, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - MAD TEA PARTY, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - MAD TEA PARTY, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Mariana Bell, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Morwenna Lasko and Jay, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - My RADIO, 7/23/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Nathan Moore partial, 7/23/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Luminescent Illuminati, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - OLD TIME DANCE, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Old Time Dance Revival 1 of 2, 7/26/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Old Time Dance Revival 2 of 2, 7/26/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Pete Francis ft. Barefoot Truth, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Raw Dawg, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - R.I.S.E/Forrow in the Dark pt. 1, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Rogan Brothers/Electric Chamelon, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Rooster Blues, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Rooster Blues, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Rose's Pawn Shop, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The Sadies, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The Sadies, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Samantha Crain & the Midnight Shivers, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Skip Shirey, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The Smart Bros., 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Sol Driven Train, 7/26/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Stephanie Rooker, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Steve Johnson Band, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Stop Drop & Roll, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Toubab Krewe *then power out, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Transmittens, 7/26/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The WAVE, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - William Walter & Co., 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Wlliam Walter & Co. #1, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Yard Dogs #2, 2009 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Zydeco Cha Cha pt. 2, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Farewell, 7/26/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Nathan & The Zydeco Cha Chas #2, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - The New Families, 7/25/09 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Luminescence Orchestra, 7/24/09 (Volume Binder 2)
  - 6.7 Floyd Fest 7, July 24-27, 2008
    - Avett Brothers 1 of 2, 7/27/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Avett Brothers 2 of 2, 7/27/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Blueground Undergrass, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Cashmere Jungle Lords, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - David Shultz, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - DJ Williams, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Donna the Buffalo 1 of 2, 7/24/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Donna the Buffalo 2 of 2, 7/24/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Everybody Fields, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Eymarel, 7/24/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Farewell Drifters, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Golom, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Ivan Neville's Dumpstaphunk 1 of 2, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Ivan Neville's Dumpstaphunk 2 of 2, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Izzy & Chris, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Jan Smith Duo, 7/27/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Jenny Arnau, 7/24/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Jenny Arnau, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Josh Phillips Folk Fest, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Jordan Harman Band, 7/24/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Jan Smith, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Kat Mills, 7/27/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Katie Pearlman Band, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Kill Basa Bill, 7/28/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Kings of Belmont 1 of 2, 7/24/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Kings of Belmont 2 of 2, 7/24/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Laura Reed & Deep Pocket 1 of 2, 7/24/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Medrone, 7/24/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Moossa, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - New Monsoon, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - New Monsoon 1 of 2, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - New Monsoon 2 of 2, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - No Speed Limit, 7/27/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Oliver Mtukudzi 1 of 2, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Oliver Mtukudzi 2 of 2, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Oneside, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Rolling Green, 7/25/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Superpowers, 7/26/08 (Volume Binder 2)
    - Tony Trischka, 7/27/08 (Volume Binder 2)
  - 6.8 Floyd Fest 9, July 22-25, 2010
    - 3 Minute Lovin, 2010 (Volume Binder 3)
    - Adrienne Young, 7/23/10 (Volume Binder 3)